<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>https://ohlinger.co/</id><title>Kyhle Öhlinger</title><subtitle>Hi all, My name is Kyhle Öhlinger and this blog post forms part of my personal blog. If you enjoy any of the posts, feel free to reach out and let me know :) </subtitle> <updated>2025-08-29T14:40:47-04:00</updated> <author> <name>Kyhle Öhlinger</name> <uri>https://ohlinger.co/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://ohlinger.co/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="https://ohlinger.co/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2025 Kyhle Öhlinger </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Creating a Chrome Extension to Query Multiple LLMs</title><link href="https://ohlinger.co/posts/creating-a-chrome-extension/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Creating a Chrome Extension to Query Multiple LLMs" /><published>2025-08-29T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2025-08-29T14:40:16-04:00</updated> <id>https://ohlinger.co/posts/creating-a-chrome-extension/</id> <content src="https://ohlinger.co/posts/creating-a-chrome-extension/" /> <author> <name>kyhle</name> </author> <category term="Technical" /> <category term="AI &amp; LLMs" /> <summary> I’ve been increasingly bouncing between ChatGPT, Gemini, and Claude depending on the task. LLMs are powerful but I tend to lose track of my open tabs quite frequently. I was thinking about methods that could make it easier to send questions to LLMs from different web pages and came up with the idea of a browser extension. You may say “but Kyhle, don’t they have their own implementations which a... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Exporting DLP Data from Slack</title><link href="https://ohlinger.co/posts/slack-dlp-data-export/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exporting DLP Data from Slack" /><published>2025-08-15T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2025-08-15T06:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://ohlinger.co/posts/slack-dlp-data-export/</id> <content src="https://ohlinger.co/posts/slack-dlp-data-export/" /> <author> <name>kyhle</name> </author> <category term="Technical" /> <category term="Random" /> <summary> This blog post and associated script assume that you have the ability to Manage DLP for your Slack / your organizations Slack. Slack’s native data export functionality, even on Enterprise Grid plans, is not a perfect solution. While it can provide access to messages and files, the format and process present significant challenges. For audit logs, data can be exported as raw JSON or CSV fil... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Wiz's Cloud Hunting Games - The ExfilCola Incident</title><link href="https://ohlinger.co/posts/wiz-cloud-hunting-games/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wiz's Cloud Hunting Games - The ExfilCola Incident" /><published>2025-05-12T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2025-05-12T06:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://ohlinger.co/posts/wiz-cloud-hunting-games/</id> <content src="https://ohlinger.co/posts/wiz-cloud-hunting-games/" /> <author> <name>kyhle</name> </author> <category term="Technical" /> <category term="Cloud IR" /> <summary> Wiz recently released the Cloud Hunting Games featuring the The ExfilCola Incident CTF. The goal of the challenge is to step into the shoes of an incident response expert, unfold the steps of the attacker, trace them back to the initial access point, and make sure that the secret formula is safe. This blog post contains the methods that I used while completing this challenge - if you are readi... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Setting up Logging and Billing for GCP Projects using Terraform</title><link href="https://ohlinger.co/posts/centralizing-gcp-logging/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Setting up Logging and Billing for GCP Projects using Terraform" /><published>2025-04-01T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2025-04-02T11:27:42-04:00</updated> <id>https://ohlinger.co/posts/centralizing-gcp-logging/</id> <content src="https://ohlinger.co/posts/centralizing-gcp-logging/" /> <author> <name>kyhle</name> </author> <category term="Technical" /> <category term="Google Cloud Platform" /> <summary> This is the link to the GitHub repository that you can use to set up logging within your environments! I have been working on a creating an open source GCP threat hunting lab (to be released later this year..) and during that time the importance having the ability to; automate the creation of several projects, capture logging in a central repository, and create billing alerts automatically... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Creating a Basic Streamlit Application for Fabric Formatted Prompts</title><link href="https://ohlinger.co/posts/using-streamlit-for-llms/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Creating a Basic Streamlit Application for Fabric Formatted Prompts" /><published>2025-03-13T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2025-03-13T06:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://ohlinger.co/posts/using-streamlit-for-llms/</id> <content src="https://ohlinger.co/posts/using-streamlit-for-llms/" /> <author> <name>kyhle</name> </author> <category term="Technical" /> <category term="AI &amp; LLMs" /> <summary> During my previous blog post, I presented a mockup for my current AI toolset. This included how I generally make use of different products / tools and try to combine them into different solutions on a daily basis. Overview of my Current AI Usage The idea behind this post was finding a way to combine prompt-engineering with a simple frontend to assist in learning more about GCP. Using the met... </summary> </entry> </feed>
